Guide to the Vassar College Dean of the College, Dean of the Faculty Records, 1917-1997 (bulk 1940-1996
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Seven College Conference (Box 90)
- Off-Campus (Box 90)
- Parietals (Box 90)
- New Programs (Box 90)
- Minnewaska Conference (Box 90)
- Library, 1964-1967; (2 folders) (Box 91)
- Library, 1967-1969 (Box 91)
- Multidisciplinary, 1972; (3 folders) (Box 91)
- Multidisciplinary - Science, Technology, and Society (STS), 1972-1973 (Box 91)
- Multidisciplinary - Man and the Human Community, 1969-1971; (2 folders) (Box 91)
- Committee Overview (Box 91)
- John Wilkie (Box 91)
- Joint College Committee (Box 91)
- Committee on Coeducation (Box 91)
- Urban Studies Committee (Box 91)
- Urban Studies (Mr. Roger Katan) (Box 91)
- Student Government (Box 91)
- Medical School, (2 folders) (Box 91)
- New York Residence, (3 folders) (Box 91)
- Trustees Proposal Committee, (2 folders) (Box 91)
- Undergraduate Structure Reform (Box 91)
- Steering Committee Agenda, (2 folders) (Box 91)
- AVRC, 1987-1988 (Box 92)
- Academic Computer Center, 1987-1988 (Box 92)
- Auditoria Study, 1984 (Box 92)
- Admission, 1986-1987 (Box 92)
- Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities (CICU), 1982-1988 (Box 92)
- Commencement, 1980-1988 (Box 92)
- College Regulation Press and Information, 1980-1988 (Box 92)
- College Policy, 1980-1987 (Box 92)
- CPC, 1983-1988 (Box 92)
- Colleges (miscellaneous), 1981-1988 (Box 92)
- The Bridge, 1968 (Box 92)
- The College Board, 1984-1988 (Box 92)
- Search Committee - Chaplain, 1981 (Box 92)
- Chaplain (general), 1979-1988 (Box 92)
- Freshman Orientation, 1987 (Box 92)
- FPCC, July 1986 - Dec 1987 (Box 92)
- SIR (Box 92)
- Alumnae Tapes (Box 92)
- Classes (Box 92)
- Juliano (Box 92)
- Clubs (Box 92)
- Faculty Campaign (Box 92)
- Department Campaign Proposals (Box 92)
- Fund Drives (Box 92)
- Comprehensive Plan (Box 92)
- College Research Center, 1966 (Box 92)
- Foreign Language Resource Center Study, 1981-1986 (Box 93)
- Middle States, 1987-1988 (Box 93)
- Finances - General (Box 93)
- Financial Aid Office, 1980-1987 (Box 93)
- Presidents - Fergusson, 1984-1988 (Box 93)
- Fellowships, 1984-1989 (Box 93)
- Fees, 1980-1982 (Box 93)
- Faculty Visiting Appointment, July 1988 (Box 93)
- Merit Pay, 1987-1988 (Box 93)
- Faculty Merit Evaluations, Feb 1989 (Box 93)
- Faculty Mailings, 1987-1988 (Box 93)
- Faculty Loans, 1986-1987 (Box 93)
- Faculty Housing, 1986-1987 (Box 93)
- Faculty Handbook, 1985-1989 (Box 93)
- Faculty Development, 1984-1989 (Box 93)
- Faculty Committees, 1985-1989 (Box 93)
- Faculty Chairs, 1983-1985 (Box 93)
- Faculty Center, 1987-1988 (Box 93)
- Community, 1983-1988 (Box 93)
- Building Maintenance, 1984-1988 (Box 93)
- Benefits, 1987-1988 (Box 93)
- Development, 1986-1988 (Box 93)
- Dean of Studies, 1987-1988 (Box 93)
- Dean of Freshmen, 1987-1988 (Box 93)
- Course Enrollment, 1985-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 93)
- Comptroller's Office, 1979-1989 (Box 93)
- Committee on Quality of Residential Life, 1983-1988 (Box 93)
- Committee on Research, 1987-1988 (Box 93)
- Committees on Committees, 1986-1987 (Box 93)
- Faculty Compensation, 1984-1988 (Box 93)
- Calendar, 1980-1987 (Box 94)
- Catalog, 1980-1988 (Box 94)
- Campus Activities, 1982-1988 (Box 94)
- CCP (miscellaneous) (Box 94)
- Career Development Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 94)
- Committee on Computing, folder # 1, 1987-1988 (Box 94)
- Committee on Computing, folder #2, 1987-1988 (Box 94)
- Departmental Files: Anthro - Women's Studies, 1987-1988; (34 folders) (Box 94)
- College Course (Box 94)
- CCP - Freshman Course (Box 94)
- Chicago Hall (Box 94)
- Language Lab Chicago Hall (Box 95)
- Registrar, 1987-1988 (Box 95)
- SAC, 1987-1988 (Box 95)
- SOS, 1987-1988; (2 folders) (Box 95)
- Summer Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 95)
- URSI, 1987-1988 (Box 95)
- Brown University, 1984-1985 (Box 95)
- Academic Computing Research, 1979-1980 (Box 95)
- Word Processing, 1980-1981 (Box 95)
- Computing Committee, 1980-1986; (8 folders) (Box 95)
- Computing Committee (Box 96)
- Sloan/Other (Box 96)
- Sloan (Box 96)
- Internal Grants (Box 96)
- Sloan, 1984-1985 (Box 96)
- Sloan Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 96)
- Sloan Budget, 1983-1985; (2 folders) (Box 96)
- Sloan Workshops, 1983-1985 (Box 96)
- Sloan MIT Wellesley (TECH) Nuclear Arms Project, 1984 (Box 96)
- Sloan Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 96)
- Sloan MIT Seminars, 1983 (Box 96)
- Sloan Grant, 1982-1983 (Box 96)
- FIPSE Final Report, 1984-1985 (Box 96)
- FIPSE (Box 96)
- FIPSE Grant (Box 96)
- FIPSE Computer Literacy Program, (3 folders) (Box 96)
- Sloan - NLA Program (Box 96)
- Academic Resource Center (Box 97)
- FPCC Ath. (Box 97)
- Pre-Major Advising Sub-Committee (Box 97)
- Various Committee Reports, 1981 (Box 97)
- Tenure Ratios (Box 97)
- Sloan Initial Proposal Development C-Bunting (Box 97)
- MISC. External/Internal Grant Corresp., 1981-1983 (Box 97)
- EDUCOM, 1982-1983 (Box 97)
- FPCC Library, 1981-1982 (Box 97)
- Miscellaneous Projects, 1983-1984 (Box 97)
- Master Planning, 1980-1983 (Box 97)
- ICONIX (Box 97)
- Urban Center (Box 97)
- Benefit Proposals (Box 97)
- Administrative Computing (Box 97)
- Admissions Computing, 1981-1982 (Box 97)
- Associate Fellows, (2 folders) (Box 97)
- Committee on Computing, 1984 (Box 97)
- Committee on Computing "B", 1984-1985 (Box 97)
- Committee on Computing "A", 1984-1985 (Box 97)
- Committee on Computing - Long Range Plan, 1984 (Box 97)
- Committee on Computing - Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 97)
- Committee on Computing -Questionnaires, 1984 (Box 97)
- Committee on Computing - Subcommittee on Educational Technologies (Box 97)
- FPCC - Retirement (Box 98)
- FPCC - SAC (Box 98)
- FPCC - Sloan Grant (Box 98)
- FPCC - Suffrage, Academic (Box 98)
- FPCC - Tait, Marion (2/76 letter Re: Dean of the College Office) (Box 98)
- FPCC - Tenure (Box 98)
- Ad Hoc Advisory Committee on Computing (Box 98)
- Committee on Committees (Box 98)
- Appeal Committee (Box 98)
- Retirement, joint Committee on (Box 98)
- Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 98)
- Budget, 1987-1988; (2 folders) (Box 98)
- Receipts, 1989-1990 (Box 98)
- Back-up for House Fellows (Box 98)
- Middle States Review (Box 98)
- Budget info., 1988-1989 (Box 98)
- Computing Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 98)
- Committee on Computing - Minutes, 1987-1988; (2 folders) (Box 98)
- Classroom Video Networking, 1987 (Box 98)
- Dev. of Educational Technology, Jan 1987 (Box 98)
- Committee on Computing "B", 1986-1987 (Box 98)
- Committee on Computing minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 98)
- Committee on Computing "A,", 1986-1987 (Box 98)
- Committee on Computing "B,", 1985-1986 (Box 98)
- Committee on Computing, minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 98)
- Committee on Computing, "A,", 1985-1986 (Box 98)
- Certification Application - MAT Program (Box 98)
- Teacher Education - MAT Program, (2 folders) (Box 98)
- FPCC - Appeal Committee (Box 99)
- FPCC - Agendas of FPCC Meetings (Box 99)
- FPCC - Annual Reports (Box 99)
- FPCC - Cambridge Associates Report (Box 99)
- FPCC - Cambridge Report Reply, Part II Drafts, March 1983, July 1983 (Box 99)
- FPCC - Chaplaincy (Box 99)
- FPCC - Chron File, 1987-1988 (Box 99)
- FPCC, 1989-1990 (Box 99)
- FPCC - Chron File, 1986 (Box 99)
- FPCC - Chron File, 1985-1986 (Box 99)
- FPCC - College Planning Council (Box 99)
- FPCC - Computing (Box 99)
- FPCC - Course Evaluation Questionnaire (Box 99)
- FPCC - Dean of the College, Meetings (Box 99)
- Five College Project, (9 folders) (Box 99)
- Graduate Study Committee (Box 99)
- FPCC - Departmental Review (Box 100)
- FPCC - Departmental Responses to Departmental Review (Box 100)
- FPCC - Discrimination (Box 100)
- FPCC - Faculty Benefits (Box 100)
- FPCC - Faculty Meeting Agendas (Box 100)
- FPCC - Faculty Meetings, FPCC Items for (Box 100)
- FPCC - Faculty Morale (Box 100)
- FPCC - Faculty Review (Box 100)
- FPCC - Fees, College (Box 100)
- FPCC as a Committee (Box 100)
- FPCC - Governance, 1984-1987 (Box 100)
- FPCC - Governance, 1982-1984 (Box 100)
- FPCC - Governance, 1979-1982 (Box 100)
- FPCC - Harassment Policy (Box 100)
- FPCC - Housing, College (for Faculty, Administrators) (Box 100)
- FPCC - Language Requirement (Box 100)
- FPCC - Library (Box 100)
- FPCC - Long- Range Planning (Box 100)
- FPCC - Mellon Grants (Box 100)
- FPCC - Minutes of FPCC Meetings Miscellaneous (Box 100)
- FPCC - Parental Benefits (Box 100)
- FPCC - Physical Education (Box 100)
- FPCC - President, Meetings with (and/ or Trustees) (Box 100)
- FPCC - Presidential Evaluation (Box 100)
- FPCC - Miscellaneous (Box 100)
- Sloan Advisory, 1990 (Box 100)
- Sloan Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 100)
- Sloan Advisory, 1988-1989 (Box 100)
- Sloan Advisory Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 100)
- Sloan Advisory Committee, Correspondence and Material, copies of material, 1986-1987 (Box 100)
- Sloan Advisory Committee, Correspondence and ''yellow'' copies of material, 1984-1985 (Box 100)
- Sloan Advisory Committee, Correspondence and "yellow'' copies of material, 1983-1984 (Box 100)
- Sloan Grant Proposal (second), 3 Sep 1985 (Box 100)
- Sloan Grant Proposal (first), 3 Sep 1985 (Box 100)
- Sloan Advisory Committee - Latest Microcomputer Offer (Box 100)
- Sloan Advisory Group - Rainbow Offer Letters (Past) (Box 100)
- Sloan Advisory Group - First Year Progress Report (Box 100)
- State Master Plan, 1988 (Box 100)
- House Fellows, 1987-1989 (Box 101)
- Sloan Annual Report, 1987 (Box 101)
- Sloan Annual Report, 1988 (Box 101)
- Sloan Reports, (4 folders) (Box 101)
- Sloan, 1986 (Box 101)
- Sloan, (2 folders) (Box 101)
- Sloan Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 101)
- Dean's Entertainment Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 101)
- URSI Dinner (Box 101)
- H Patrick Sullivan (Box 101)
- Entertainment, 1987-1988 (Box 101)
- Help for Doing Faculty Publishing (Box 101)
- State of New York Education Department Visit and Schedule, 1988 (Box 101)
- Visiting Committees, 1987-1988 (Box 101)
- Department/Program Review, 1988-1989; (2 folders) (Box 101)
- United Way (Box 101)
- Residential Life Committee (Box 101)
- Ford Scholars' Tea (Box 101)
- Studio Art / Kenyon Project, 1988 (Box 101)
- Language Assistants, 1987-1988 (Box 101)
- FPCC, 1972-1978; (3 folders) (Box 102)
- Figures given to Miss Tait for FPCC, Apr 1975 (Box 102)
- FPCC, 1967-1972 (Box 102)
- Committee on Faculty Housing (Box 102)
- Language Assistants [Personnel], 1988-1990; (4 folders) (Box 102)
- Committee on Computing (Box 102)
- Betty Cobb (Box 102)
- Center for Advanced Study and Behavioral Sciences (Box 102)
- Surveys (Box 102)
- The Deans' Cage, 1987-1990; (3 folders) (Box 102)
- Marching List, 1988-1989 (Box 102)
- Japanese Dean Visit (Box 102)
- Sanders Move, 1989 (Box 102)
- FPCC: Chronological, 1983-1985; (2 folders) (Box 102)
- Committee on Fellowships (Box 103)
- Committee on Lectures, Funds, (3 folders) (Box 103)
- Committee on the Library (Box 103)
- East Asian Studies, 1961 - June 1969; (2 folders) (Box 103)
- East Asian Studies Annual Reports (Box 103)
- Education, 1943 - June 1971 (Box 103)
- English, July 1965 - Aug 1971 (Box 103)
- Geology-Geography, Nov 1965 - Dec 1971 (Box 103)
- Science Library (Box 103)
- Committee on Master Planning, 1972-1974; (2 folders) (Box 103)
- Field Work, 1963-1964; (4 folders) (Box 104)
- History, 1965 - June 1973; (3 folders) (Box 104)
- Music, Aug 1965 - June 1973 (Box 104)
- Budgets - Miscellaneous, (7 folders) (Box 104)
- Budgets - Miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box 105)
- Sub Rosa (Box 105)
- Research Committee - New Leave System, (2 folders) (Box 105)
- Performing Arts Center (Box 105)
- Ad hoc Committee on Priorities (Box 105)
- Proxy Review Committee (Box 105)
- General Committee on Research (Box 105)
- Research Committee, Grants in Aid Letters, Annual Report, 1969; (2 folders) (Box 105)
- Committee on Research, Faculty Leave Applications, 1975-1980; (5 folders) (Box 105)
- Ad hoc Committee on Sanders Chemistry Building (Box 106)
- Committee on Scholarships and Financial Aid (Box 106)
- Committee on Science, Technology, and Society (Box 106)
- Committee of Seven (Box 106)
- Committee on Sexual Harassment (Box 106)
- Special Services Advisory Committee (Box 106)
- Ad hoc Committee on the Status of Women at Vassar (Box 106)
- Steering Committee for Macy Grant (Box 106)
- Ad hoc Committee on Student Evaluations, (2 folders) (Box 106)
- ACMHA-Intercollegiate Resource Center, Student Co-ordinating Committee (Box 106)
- Committee on Student Records (Box 106)
- Freshman Year Task Force (Box 106)
- Teaching Task Force (Box 106)
- Third World Studies Committee (Box 106)
- Mellon Committee, 1962-1965; (2 folders) (Box 106)
- House Fellows, 1951-1979 (Box 106)
- Housing Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 106)
- Huber Foundation (Box 106)
- Humanities, 1967-1969 (Box 106)
- IBM-Vassar Exchange Agreement, 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box 106)
- Immigration Procedures, 1972 (Box 106)
- India Seminar, 1967 (Box 106)
- India Women's College Exchange Program, 1967-1970 (Box 106)
- Inquires, Evening, Summer Special, 1970-1979 (Box 106)
- Institute of International Education (Box 106)
- IRS, 1968-1979 (Box 106)
- Intercultural Center, 1977 (Box 106)
- International Cooperation Year, 1965 (Box 106)
- The International Council on the Future of the University, 1974-1978 (Box 106)
- International Education Act, 1967 (Box 106)
- International Exchange of Persons, 1968-1979 (Box 106)
- International Studies Program, 1976 (Box 106)
- International Womens' Year, 1975-1977 (Box 106)
- International Year of the Child (Box 106)
- Junior Year Abroad, 1968-1979 (Box 106)
- Department Key Assignments (Box 106)
- Keys, 1949-1977 (Box 106)
- DOF - Annual Report, 1962-1968 (Box 106)
- Department Chairmen Elections, 1974-1976; (2 folders) (Box 106)
- Committee on American Culture Program (Box 107)
- Financial Planning Committee (Box 107)
- DOF - Annual Report, 1969 (Box 107)
- Campus Committee on Student Life (Box 107)
- Campaign Executive Committee, (2 folders) (Box 107)
- Ad hoc Campus Security Committee (Box 107)
- Miscellaneous (Box 107)
- Tom Matos, 1991-1992 (Box 107)
- James Mundy, 1991-1992 (Box 107)
- Planning and Priorities Committee (Box 107)
- Recruitment (Box 107)
- Safety Committee (Box 107)
- John Savarese (Box 107)
- SOS, 1991-1992; (3 folders) (Box 107)
- Staff Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 107)
- Sandy Thompson, 1991-1992 (Box 107)
- Peter Tveskov, 1991-1992 (Box 107)
- Trustees - Academic Affairs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 107)
- Trustees - Budget Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 108)
- Trustees - General, 1991-1992 (Box 108)
- Diversity Series (Box 108)
- Faculty Salaries (Box 108)
- Clare Booth Luce Fund (Box 108)
- Minority Candidate Prospects (Box 108)
- Peggy McIntosh visit, Jan 1929 - Jan 1930 (Box 108)
- Multicultural Curriculum Taskforce (Box 108)
- Nursery School Taskforce (Box 108)
- Organization of American Historians (OAH) (Box 108)
- Science Taskforce (Box 108)
- Dept./Program Chairs Survey, (2 folders) (Box 108)
- Vassar Information (Box 108)
- Key to Comparative Information (Box 108)
- Faculty Questionnaire (Box 108)
- Wesleyan (Box 108)
- Mt. Holyoke (Box 108)
- Bryn Mawr (Box 108)
- Bowdoin (Box 108)
- Colgate (Box 109)
- Williams (Box 109)
- Smith (Box 109)
- Wellesley (Box 109)
- Amherst (Box 109)
- Carleton (Box 109)
- AC 280 Dye/Bergon (Box 109)
- Acting President (Box 109)
- Carol Barnes, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- CCP, 1991-1992; (2 folders) (Box 109)
- Committee on Computing, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- Faculty Meeting Speeches, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- FASC, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- Frances D. Fergusson, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- FCC, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- FPCC, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- Harvey Flad, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- Mike Fraher, (2 folders) (Box 109)
- Swarthmore (Box 109)
- Reed (Box 109)
- President's File (Box 109)
- Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- Budget Retreat, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- Chairs' Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- Ken Cool, 1991-1992 (Box 109)
- Garval, Michael (Box 110)
- Chessid, Dr. Ilona (Box 110)
- Dan Giannini, 1991-1992 (Box 110)
- Clare Graham, 1991-1992 (Box 110)
- Sally Griffen, 1991-1992 (Box 110)
- Chuck Henry, 1991-1992 (Box 110)
- Andy Jennings, 1991-1992 (Box 110)
- Dean's Entertainment Budget, 1988-1991; (3 folders) (Box 110)
- Majors Committee Meetings with Dean (Box 110)
- Budget Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 110)
- Budget Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 110)
- Opening Days, 1989-1990 (Box 110)
- Department Chairs and Program Directors Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 110)
- Department and Program Review, 1989-1990 (Box 110)
- Visiting Professors; Blue Cross, Furniture Rental, etc., 1987-1988 (Box 110)
- Kathy Brown Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 110)
- I-9 Correspondence, 1989-1991; (2 folders) (Box 110)
- Who to Call Lists (Box 110)
- Language Assistant, 1990-1991 (Box 110)
- Faculty Forum, 1989-1990 (Box 110)
- Walter Fairservis Computer Survey, 1984 (Box 110)
- C.W.A. Original Negotiating, 1986 (Box 110)
- Budget Sheets, Comparison, 1976-1981; (2 folders) (Box 110)
- Committee on Computing, 1988-1989 (Box 110)
- Job Advertisements (Box 111)
- EA Clark Symposium, 1985-1999; (13 folders) (Box 111)
- EA Clark Symposium, 1985-1989; (5 folders) (Box 112)
- Berkshire Conference, 1992-1993; (2 folders) (Box 112)
- Index to Faculty Rules (Box 112)
- Distinguished Alumnae, (2 folders) (Box 112)
- Ford EAC History of College (Box 112)
- College Charter (Box 112)
- Chronology of College Charter, (2 folders) (Box 112)
- Ely Renovation (Box 112)
- Computer Center Renovation (Box 112)
- Academic & Administrative Computing Merge (Box 112)
- S.I.S. Minutes, 1985-1987; (2 folders) (Box 112)
- Microcomputer Purchases, 1983-1986; (4 folders) (Box 112)
- Incoming Mail, 1985 (Box 113)
- AT & T Contract, 1985 (Box 113)
- Committee on Computing, 1983 - 1987; (4 folders) (Box 113)
- Sloan Steering committee, 1984 (Box 113)
- Progress Report, Oct 1989 (Box 113)
- Sloan Liberal Arts Project Phase II (Box 113)
- Sloan Renewal Budget, 1985-1989 (Box 113)
- Sloan Progress Report, Sep 1986 (Box 113)
- Sloan Swarthmore Meeting, June 1986 (Box 113)
- Sloan Syllabi (Box 113)
- Sloan, 1986-1987 (Box 113)
- Sloan Special Leave Grants, 1985-1986 (Box 114)
- Sloan Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 114)
- Sloan Renewal Grant, 1985-1986 (Box 114)
- Sloan Progress Report, May 1991 (Box 114)
- Sloan Progress Report, Nov 1988 (Box 114)
- Sloan, 1989-1991 (Box 114)
- Sloan Final Report, etc. (Box 114)
- Pew Grant Proposal, Spring 1986 (Box 114)
- Pew Science Program (Box 114)
- Luce Initiative (Box 114)
- NEH Prof. Grant (Box 114)
- Jove (NASA) (Box 114)
- Hughes, 1989-1992; (3 folders) (Box 114)
- CS File, 1988-1989 (Box 114)
- Hughes Study GP, 1987-1988 (Box 114)
- Hughes (Box 114)
- Annual Reports (Box 114)
- Original Proposal and Related Correspondence (Box 114)
- Dinner, 12 Apr 1989 (Box 114)
- Budget and Equipment (Box 114)
- Faculty Positions (Box 114)
- Steering Committee (Box 114)
- Miscellaneous (Box 114)
- Course Selection Study, (2 folders) (Box 114)
- Keck Proposal, 1991 (Box 114)
- CCP, 1990-1992; (2 folders) (Box 115)
- Library Serials (Box 115)
- General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 115)
- CC's of Various Letters from NSD, 1989-1991 (Box 115)
- CC's of NSD Correspondence, 1991 (Box 115)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 115)
- PEW Proposal, 1990 (Box 115)
- Hughes, 1989 (Box 115)
- Fieldwork Subcommittee (Box 115)
- Job Advertisements (Box 115)
- Library Speech (Box 115)
- Recruitment, 1990-1991 (Box 115)
- Safety Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 115)
- John Savarese, 1990-1991 (Box 115)
- Science Brochure, 1990-1991 (Box 115)
- SOS, 1990-1991 (Box 115)
- SOS Budget Retreat, 1990 (Box 115)
- Staff Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 115)
- Trustees - Academic Affairs Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 115)
- Trustees - General, 1990-1991 (Box 115)
- Trustees - Budget Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 115)
- Academic Planning (Box 115)
- Admission (Box 115)
- Art Gallery (Box 115)
- Athletics (Box 115)
- Carol Barnes (AVRC), (2 folders) (Box 115)
- Capital Campaign (Box 115)
- Capital Budget (Box 115)
- CCP Agenda / Minutes (Box 116)
- CCP, (4 folders) (Box 116)
- Student Majors (Box 116)
- Chairs Meeting (Box 116)
- Computer Requests (Box 116)
- Committee on Computing (Box 116)
- Ken Cool (Box 116)
- CPC (Box 116)
- Development Priorities (Box 116)
- Faculty Retreat (Box 116)
- FASC (Box 116)
- FCC Report, 1989 (Box 116)
- Fran Fergusson (Box 116)
- FPCC (Box 116)
- Dan Giannini / Registrar (Box 116)
- Career Development (Box 116)
- Internationalizing the Curriculum (Box 116)
- Colton Johnson / Dean of Studies (Box 116)
- Legal Workshop for Chairs (Box 117)
- Library (Box 117)
- Natalie Marshall (Box 117)
- Jim Montoya (Box 117)
- Recruitment (Box 117)
- SAC (Box 117)
- Safety Committee (Box 117)
- Stephen Saulis (Box 117)
- John Savarese (Box 117)
- Dixie Sheridan (Box 117)
- SOS (Box 117)
- Staff Meeting (Box 117)
- Tony Stellato (Box 117)
- Trustees - Academic Affairs Committee (Box 117)
- Trustees - General (Box 117)
- Trustees - Budget Committee (Box 117)
- Administration Computing Requests, 1989-1990; (2 folders) (Box 117)
- Admissions, 1987-1991; (4 folders) (Box 117)
- Travel, 1991 (Box 117)
- Affirmative Action, 1986-1991; (3 folders) (Box 117)
- Affirmative Action Reports (Box 118)
- American Collegiate Consortium, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- American Collegiate Consortium for EW (Box 118)
- American Council on Education, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Ad Search (Box 118)
- Art Gallery News (Box 118)
- Computing Plans (Box 118)
- Director of Theatre Search (Box 118)
- DOS Nomination Committee (Box 118)
- Faculty Retreat (Box 118)
- Faculty Salary Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Hilary Goldhammer (Box 118)
- History 381 (Box 118)
- Head Librarian Search Committee (Box 118)
- Museum Director Art Gallery (Box 118)
- Tracy Nichols (Box 118)
- Sit In, Feb 1990 (Box 118)
- Morgan Stanley (Box 118)
- Robin Walker (Box 118)
- Art Gallery, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Athletics, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Carol Barnes, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Capital Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Chairs' Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- CCP, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- College Course Program, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Committee on Computing, 1990-1991; (2 folders) (Box 118)
- Ken Cool, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- FASC, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Frances D. Fergusson, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Dan Giannini, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Clare Graham, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Colton Johnson, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Chris Kimm, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- Library, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
- CPC, 1990-1991 (Box 119)
- FCC, 1990-1991 (Box 119)
- FPCC, 1990-1991 (Box 119)
- Association of American Colleges (AAC) (Box 119)
- AAUP, 1987-1991; (2 folders) (Box 119)
- AAVC, 1986-1990 (Box 119)
- ACC, 1987-1991; (9 folders) (Box 119)
- Academic Enrichment Program, 1986-1990 (Box 119)
- Academic Program Development, 1987-1991; (2 folders) (Box 119)
- Academic Resource Center, 1986-1991; (2 folders) (Box 119)
- Academic Space, 1981-1989 (Box 119)
- ACUSNY, 1990-1991; (2 folders) (Box 119)
- Department and Program Files, 1988-1991; (48 folders) (Box 120)
- Department and Program Files, 1988-1991; (36 folders) (Box 121)
- Department and Program Files, 1988-1991; (44 folders) (Box 122)
- Library Annual Reports, Dean's Copy, 1990-1991 (Box 122)
- CCP - Agenda/Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 122)
- Taskforce on Science (Box 122)
- Taskforce - Multicultural Curriculum (Box 122)
- Sudan Studies Association Dinner, 9 April 1992 (Box 123)
- NEH Hudson River Conference, 14 June - 16 July 1992 (Box 123)
- Ellen Chesler - Lecture and Dinner, 26 Mar 1992 (Box 123)
- American Culture - Travel (Box 123)
- American Culture Conference - Menus, Set-ups, 1992 (Box 123)
- American Studies - NEH Conference, 1992 (Box 123)
- Peggy McIntosh Visit, 1992 (Box 123)
- Taskforce on International and Feminist Scholarship, 1989 (Box 123)
- Visitors and Consultants, 1988-1989 (Box 123)
- House Fellows' Orientation (Box 123)
- New Faculty I-9, 1991-1993; (2 folders) (Box 123)
- Comparative World Views Group (Box 123)
- Department/Program Review, 1990-1991 (Box 123)